Guide to the Foster Hall Collection, 1800-1952 CAM.FHC.2011.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Published Sheet Music, 1841-1900; IV.
  - Eulalie, [between 1856 and 1883], c1851
  - Eulalie, [between 1856 and 1862], c1851
    New York: Firth, Pond & Co. Pittsburgh: H. Kleber & Bro.
  - Eulalie, [between 1863 and 1866], c1851
  - Eulalie, [1867?], c1851
  - Eulalie, c1851
  - Fairy Belle, c1859
  - Fairy Belle, c1859
  - Fairy Belle, c1859
  - Fairy Belle, [ca. 1863], c1859
  - Fairy Belle, 1861-1865
    New Orleans: A.E. Blackmar & Bro.
  - Fairy Belle, [between 1867 and 1876], c1859
  - Fairy Belle, [1860?], c1859
  - Fairy Belle, [1863?], c1859
  - Fairy Belle, [1862?], c1859
  - Fairy Belle, [1865?], c1859
  - Fairy Belle, c1859
  - Fairy Belle, [1864?], c1859
  - Fairy Belle, [1860?], c1859
  - Fairy Belle, [1864?], c1859
  - Fairy Belle, 1861-1865
  - Fairy Belle, [1860?], c1859
  - Fairy Belle, [between 1901 and 1904], c1859
  - Fairy Belle, 1861-1865
    Augusta, GA: Blackmar & Bro.
  - Fairy Belle, [1889?], c1859
    Boston: Oliver Ditson Co.
  - Fairy Belle, 1861-1865
  - Fairy Belle, [between 1867 and 1876], c1859
  - Farewell Mother Dear, c1861
    New York: John J. Daly
  - Farewell mother dear: admired ballad, 1861-1899
  - Farewell my Lilly dear, 1855-1899
  - Farewell my Lilly dear, 1900-1920
    Chicago: National Music Co.
  - Farewell my Lilly dear; arr, [between 1856 and 1862], c1853
  - Farewell my Lilly dear: a plantation melody, c1853
  - Farewell my Lilly dear, c1851
  - Farewell my Lilly dear, [between 1867 and 1876], c1851
  - Farewell my Lilly dear, [between 1856 and 1862], c1851
  - Farewell my Lilly dear, c1851
  - Farewell my Lilly dear, [between 1856 and 1862], c1851
  - Farewell my Lilly dear, c1851
  - Farewell my Lilly dear, c1851
  - Farewell my Lilly dear, c1851
  - Farewell my Lilly dear, c1851
  - Farewell my Lilly dear, 1855-1899
  - Farewell my Lilly dear, c1851
  - Farewell old cottage, c1851
    New York: Firth, Pond & Co. New Orleans: Wm.T. Mayo
  - Farewell old cottage, [186-?], c1851
  - Farewell old cottage, c1863
  - Farewell, sweet mother, [between 1863 and 1877], c1961 [i.e. 1861]
  - Farewell, sweet mother, 1861-1899
  - Farewell, sweet mother, [between 1889 and 1896], c1889
  - Farewell, sweet mother, [between 1863 and 1877], c1961 [i.e. 1861]
  - Farewell, sweet mother, c1961 [i.e. 1861]
    New York: Firth, Pond & Co
  - Farewell, sweet mother, [between 1889 and 1896], c1889
  - For the dear old flag I die!, c1863
  - For thee, love, for thee, [between 1863 and 1866], c1859
  - For thee, love, for thee, c1859
  - Gentle Annie, 1856-1863
    London: Addison, Hollier & Lucas
  - Gentle Annie, 1856-1899
  - Gentle Annie, 1879-1890
    London: Chappell & Co.
  - Gentle Annie, 1856-1899
  - Gentle Annie, [between 1863 and 1877], c1857
  - Gentle Annie, 1860-1866
    London: The Music-Publishing Co.
  - Gentle Annie, 1856-1899
  - Gentle Annie, 1857-1883
  - Gentle Annie, 1856-1890
    London: Brewer & Co.
  - Gentle Annie, c1857
  - Gentle Annie, 1856-1899
  - Gentle Annie, 1858-1888
  - Gentle Annie, 1856-1899
  - Gentle Annie, 1856-1899
  - Gentle Annie, [1858?]
  - Gentle Annie, 1903-1941
    London: F. Pitman & Hart
  - Gentle Annie, c1857
  - Gentle Annie, c1857
  - Gentle Annie, 1858-1888
  - Gentle Annie, c1856
  - Gentle Annie, c1856
  - Gentle Annie, c1856
  - Gentle Annie, [1863?]
  - Gentle Annie, [between 1877 and 1889], c1856
  - Gentle Annie, 1882-1899
  - Gentle Annie, c1856
  - Gentle Annie, c1856
  - Gentle Annie, c1856
  - Gentle Annie, c1856
  - Gentle Annie, c1856
  - Gentle Annie, c1856
  - Gentle Annie, c1856
  - Gentle Annie, c1856
  - Gentle Annie, 1856-1899
  - Gentle Annie, 1856-1899
  - Gentle Annie, c1884
  - Gentle Annie, c1858
  - Gentle Annie, [1860?], c1858
  - Gentle Annie: for the guitar, [between 1877 and 1896], c1857
  - Gentle Lena Clare, c1862
  - Gentle Lena Clare, c1862
  - Gentle Lena Clare, [between 1863 and 1866], c1862
  - Give the stranger happy cheer, c1850 [i.e. 1851]
  - Give the stranger happy cheer, c1850 [i.e. 1851]
  - Give this to mother, c1864
    New York: H. Waters
  - Give this to mother, c1864
    New York: P.A. Wundermann
  - Give us this day our daily bread, 1863
- Forgeries, 1934-1945; V.
  - Correspondence re: Weisberg Levitt Forgery, 1936-1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Forgery "I Will Be True to Thee" and Dichter Correspondence, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Forgery "The Doctor of Alcantara", No date (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Foster Forgery Henry Kirschenbaum Manuscript and Correspondence, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Kirschenbaum, Henry Questionable ms., 1935-1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Forgeries Possibly from Levitt/Weisberg, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Charles Levitt and Weisberg Forgeries, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 7)